<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advanced Audit Logging on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advanced Audit Logging on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/audit-log/advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit Log Overview</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/advanced/overview/</guid>
      <description>Once you&amp;rsquo;ve started sending events into your Audit Log, it&amp;rsquo;s time to explore some of the advanced functionality.
Display Templates Display templates allow you to customize the display of audit events, after the event has been received. The events are still immutable. The display templates implement a rules engine that is applied when the event is rendered. This simply adds an additional field to the event, and can be excluded at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Templates</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/display-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/advanced/display-templates/</guid>
      <description>Display templates is an important part of controlling how the events are rendered in the browser, exports or over any other stream.
A display template has the following components:
Definitions Name The name is internal only to the admin site. This is a place for you to record what the template is attempting to do.
Rules The rules field is a collection of rules that will be evaluated by the Replicated Audit Log rules engine to determine if this template shoud be applied to the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH Event Streaming</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/ssh-streaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/advanced/ssh-streaming/</guid>
      <description>SSH Event Streaming allows Enterprise API users to stream events as they occur over ssh using an Enterprise API Token.
Usage To use the SSH event streaming feature, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to start by getting an Enterprise API token.
To open a stream for your sandbox, connect to tail.auditlog.replicated.com using your Enterprise API token as the username:
ssh aeb1c315b9a8ed11a3f998d8e8ff@tail.auditlog.replicated.com  Once the connection is open, CSV events will begin to stream through stdout, and can be piped to a file or other event ingest system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Template Comparators</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/template-comparators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/advanced/template-comparators/</guid>
      <description>The following values are acceptable for &amp;ldquo;comparator&amp;rdquo; field in rules in the Replicated Audit Log rules engine:
   Comparator Desscription     eq Matches when the value is equal to the event object data at path. This compares values only and doesn&amp;rsquo;t compare types.   is The same as eq but it also compares types of objects.   neq Matches when the value is not equal to the event object data at path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Publisher Versions</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/tracking-versions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/advanced/tracking-versions/</guid>
      <description>When sending events to your Audit Log, consumers of the Publisher API may send event metadata like the name and version of the vendor component that is sending the events. A minimal event payload that includes this metadata might look like
{ &amp;quot;action&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;user.login&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;crud&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;c&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;group&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;id&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;7890123&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;name&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;some.customer&amp;quot; }, &amp;quot;actor&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;id&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;123456&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;name&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;user@example.com&amp;quot; }, &amp;quot;component&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;authentication-api&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;version&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;ae242df&amp;quot; }  Where component describes a single versioned piece of a architecture like authentication-api or spreadsheet-processor and version is usually one of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Events</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/advanced/automated-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/advanced/automated-events/</guid>
      <description>When an end customer uses a Viewer or Enterprise token to view logs directly from the Publisher API, the Replicated Audit Log will record the read event in your audit log.
You can configure these events with the optional view_log_action parameter when you create a new Viewer or Enterprise token through the Publisher API. The default action is &amp;ldquo;audit.log.view&amp;rdquo;. Viewer tokens also require an actor_id parameter at creation time, while Enterprise token audit events generate an actor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>