<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Distributing a Swarm Application on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/categories/distributing-a-swarm-application/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Distributing a Swarm Application on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/distributing-a-swarm-application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Nodes</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/add-nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/add-nodes/</guid>
      <description>When it is necessary to add additional nodes to satisfy the scheduling requirements of an application, Replicated makes it easy for the end customer to add additional Swarm nodes on remote instances to run a distributed application.
On the Cluster page on the Admin Console an &amp;ldquo;Add Node&amp;rdquo; button will be visible. This will prompt the end customer with two simple options for adding a node.
Scripted Installation The scripted install is the recommended means for adding an additional node to the Swarm cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airgapped Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/airgapped-installations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/airgapped-installations/</guid>
      <description>tar xzvf replicated.tar.gz cat ./swarm-init.sh | sudo bash -s airgap   Download &amp;amp; Rename Airgap Package  On the license properties page in the vendor portal, enable Airgap installations for this license and copy the download link. This URL is designed to be delivered to that customer. They will use this link to download current airgap packages when you promote a release. When they download new airgap packages to their server, it is important that your customer set the --trust-server-names and --content-disposition flags for wget or rename the file to something ending with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Replicated</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/installing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/installing/</guid>
      <description>We distribute an installation script that can be used to install Replicated into a new or existing Swarm cluster. The cluster does not have to be created at this point, the Replicated install script can install Docker Engine and provision a new Swarm cluster.
 Basic install (recommended):  The basic install will install Docker (as needed) and Replicated. It will save the install script to a file which you can inspect and then run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing to an Existing Cluster</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/installing-manually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/installing-manually/</guid>
      <description>The advanced Swarm install requires the host is running Docker with a version between 1.13.1 - 17.06.2-ce.
This method will save the Docker Compose YAML to a file and then run a command using the YAML file as the input. We recommend reading and understanding the Compose file prior to running.
docker swarm init curl -sSL -o docker-compose.yml &amp;quot;https://get.replicated.com/docker-compose.yml?swarm_node_address=$(docker info --format &#39;{{.Swarm.NodeAddr}}&#39;)&amp;quot; docker node update --label-add replicated-role=master &amp;quot;$(docker info --format &#39;{{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Swarm Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Swarm Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/overview/</guid>
      <description>Once you have packaged your application for Replicated on Swarm, it is time to distribute it to your customers. This documentation contains everything needed to successfully install and manage customer installations using Replicated for Docker Swarm. Help installing Replicated on Docker Swarm is available through the Replicated community or by email at contact@replicated.com.
The Installing section contains all of the documentation for provisioning Docker Swarm clusters and installing Replicated, whether it is through the easy install script, a manual installation, or an airgapped installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported Operating Systems</title>
      <link>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/supported-operating-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/swarm/customer-installations/supported-operating-systems/</guid>
      <description>Replicated supports Linux-based servers that can run current versions of Docker.
Your machine must support docker-engine 1.13.1 - 17.06.2-ce (with 17.06.2-ce being the recommended version). This also requires a 64-bit distribution with a kernel minimum of 3.10.
Replicated provides an easy install script for Swarm that works with the the following list of operating systems:
 Debian 7.7+ Ubuntu 14.04.5 / 16.04 Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7+ CentOS 7+ Oracle Linux 7+  As new operating systems start to support Docker we extend our install script and QA process to include them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>