<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes Guide on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/categories/kubernetes-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes Guide on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 04:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/kubernetes-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Kubernetes Release</title>
      <link>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/create-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/create-release/</guid>
      <description>Create and Ship a Release When starting and learning the Replicated platform, the Vendor Portal will be the place you spend most of your time. This guide is designed to help you get familiar with the concepts and ideas that are important to successfully ship your application on Replicated. If you get stuck or need help, head to our community.
This guide will deploy one of the canonical Kubernetes applications using Replicated, and then iterate on it to ship an update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing and Testing a Kubernetes Release</title>
      <link>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/install/</guid>
      <description>Installing and Testing a Kubernetes Release This guide will give you first-hand experience installing a Replicated Kubernetes appliance and the Guestbook application. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet created the Guestbook application, head back to the Create and Ship as Release guide and complete that first.
Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve created a release and promoted it to the the Unstable channel, the next step is to create a customer license and use this this license to install the application on a test server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterating and Updating</title>
      <link>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/iterate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/iterate/</guid>
      <description>Iterate and Ship Updates This guide will walk you through making a change and shipping an update to an application after it&amp;rsquo;s been deployed. It&amp;rsquo;s assumed you have the environment from parts 1 and 2 of this guide (creating a release and installing). If you haven&amp;rsquo;t completed these guides, head back and finish them first.
Now that we have a Kubernetes cluster running, a common task is to ship updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Storage</title>
      <link>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/managing-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/ship-with-kubernetes/managing-storage/</guid>
      <description>Rook  Replicated&amp;rsquo;s Kubernetes scheduler uses Rook to dynamically provision storage for Persistent Volume Claims required by Replicated and your app.
 Replication  Replicated&amp;rsquo;s install script will default to creating a cluster backed by the host directory /opt/replicated/rook. Each file in the cluster begins with a single copy, i.e. without replication. When a new node is added to the cluster, you can edit the Pool custom resource named replicapool in the rook namespace and configure it to store copies of each file on two separate hosts:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>