<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ldap and Identity on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/categories/ldap-and-identity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ldap and Identity on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/ldap-and-identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Authenticating with LDAP</title>
      <link>/docs/ldap-and-identity/authentication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/ldap-and-identity/authentication/</guid>
      <description>One feature of the Replicated LDAP integration is the ability for your application containers to authenticate using a simple REST API that runs inside your application environment. When your application container creates an authentication request against the on-prem Replicated API, Replicated will send the request to the identity provider for login and return a success/error response synchronously.
For details on using the Identity API in your application, refer to the Indentity API reference documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LDAP &amp; Identity Integration Overview</title>
      <link>/docs/ldap-and-identity/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/ldap-and-identity/overview/</guid>
      <description>Replicated can be integrated with LDAP servers to sync users and/or authenticate users between the directory and your application.
 Configuration  To enable the identity services in your application, a top level key in your release yaml must be present:
identity: enabled: true provisioner: &#39;https://localhost/ldap/auth&#39; sources: - source: ldap enabled: true     Field Description     enabled Boolean indicating if LDAP authentication is enabled on this installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported LDAP Servers</title>
      <link>/docs/ldap-and-identity/supported-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/ldap-and-identity/supported-servers/</guid>
      <description>Replicated currently supports LDAP Authentication and sync in the following directory servers:
 Microsoft Active Directory (2008 and 2012) Open LDAP LDAP 389 DS Free IPA  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>