<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Exposing Events on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Exposing Events on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exposing Event Data</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/overview/</guid>
      <description>There are two main way to expose your audit log data to your application&amp;rsquo;s users. Users can browse and search events using an embeddable viewer UI, or they can access data programmatically using API tokens.
Using the embedded viewer As a vendor, you can embed the event viewer into frontend site. For a guide to viewer features, see Using the Embedded Viewer
Using Enterprise IT Integration API Tokens In addition to the viewer, Audit events can be exposed via the Enterprise IT Integration API</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using The Retraced Viewer</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/viewer/</guid>
      <description>The Retraced embedded viewer is the easiest way consume and understand your audit log data. This guide will walk you through the viewer&amp;rsquo;s features.
Note &amp;ndash; if you&amp;rsquo;re a Software Vendor and you&amp;rsquo;re looking to embed the viewer into your site, see the Embedded Viewer Guide
Overview The viewer exposes four core features:
 Search Filters Export API Token Management.  Search The search box allows for free-text search of all audit events, but also supports some structured search operators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise API</title>
      <link>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/enterprise-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/audit-log/exposing-events/enterprise-api/</guid>
      <description>The Retraced Enterprise API enables users to consume audit log data programmatically and integrate it with an external monitoring or security system.
Creating and Managing Enterprise Tokens Enterprise Tokens can be created and managed via the Embedded Viewer
Note: If you&amp;rsquo;re a vendor integrating Retraced as your audit log, you can also manage and distribute Enterprise Tokens using the Publisher API.
Graphql The quickest way to start getting events is using the GraphQL API.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>