<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ship Guide on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/categories/ship-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ship Guide on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/ship-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Ship</title>
      <link>/guides/helm-application/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/helm-application/introduction/</guid>
      <description>About This Guide  This guide will walk you through the process of taking an existing Helm application, package it and distribute it in Replicated using Replicated Ship. For this guide, we will take the GitLab Helm charts and use them to create an easy-to-deploy application.
 Introduction to Replicated Ship  Replicated Ship is a set of tools (APIs, YAML spec, and distributable components) that make it easy to package and distribute a modern, cloud-native application for an enterprise customer to install, configure, and operate in their own private environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packaging A Helm Application</title>
      <link>/guides/helm-application/create-a-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/helm-application/create-a-release/</guid>
      <description>Create a Customer  To begin, log in (or create an account) on console.replicated.com. If you already have an account on vendor.replicated.com, you can use it here too. After signing up and activating your account, you&amp;rsquo;ll be presented with the opportunity to create a new customer. Here we&amp;rsquo;ll be using &amp;lsquo;ATestCustomer&amp;rsquo;.
 Navigate To Ship  The Ship product page can be found through the &amp;lsquo;Products&amp;rsquo; dropdown.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t visited before, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a prompt to get started with Release Channels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing The Customer Installation</title>
      <link>/guides/helm-application/installing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/helm-application/installing/</guid>
      <description>Part 3 Of A Series
This is part 3 of a guide that walks through creating a sample application in Replicated Ship. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t followed the previous sections of this guide, go back to deploying an application before following this guide.
  Installing the Release  Now we can produce an installation script for our test customer.
Copy the command from this screen, and take it to a workstation that has Docker installed, and run it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>