<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Managing Customer Installations on Replicated Help Center</title>
    <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Managing Customer Installations on Replicated Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Replicated, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/native/customer-installations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Customer Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/overview/</guid>
      <description>Once your application is packaged, it is time to distribute it to your customers. This section provides all of the information necessary to setup and manage customer installations. If you need help installing Replicated, help is available through the Replicated community or via email at contact@replicated.com.
The Installing documentation contains all of the documentation needed to install Replicated with the easy install script, manually, or as an airgapped install.
The Automating documentation provides information about completely automated installs, which are useful for both continuous integration and customers wanting to completely automate the provisioning and setup of your application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Replicated</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Before installing Replicated review the list of supported operating systems.
Replicated Version The current release of Replicated is version 2.20.2 released on April 26, 2018 . Prior versions are available and can also be installed and instructions how depend on your install method. To read about the latest features of Replicated see the Replicated changelog.
Quick Installation curl -sSL -o install.sh https://get.replicated.com/docker sudo bash ./install.sh  Pick your Install Method Easy Installation We provide an easy-to-use one-line installation process (via shell script) which will detect your OS, ask a few questions and install the Replicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported Operating Systems</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/supported-operating-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/supported-operating-systems/</guid>
      <description>Replicated supports Linux-based servers that can run current versions of Docker.
Your machine must support docker-engine 1.7.1 - 17.06.2-ce (with 17.06.2-ce being the recommended version). This also requires a 64-bit distribution with a kernel minimum of 3.10.
On some operating systems including CentOS 6 and RHEL 6, features have been backported into the kernel to allow Docker to run. It is not recommend to run Docker under a 2.x kernel and support for it is best-effort based.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Replicated</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/upgrading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/upgrading/</guid>
      <description>You can update all Replicated component versions to latest by re-running the installation script.
curl -sSL https://get.replicated.com/docker | sudo bash  If you have additional nodes that are not managed by Replicated automatic upgrades, you will independently need to run the following on each of them.
curl -sSL https://get.replicated.com/operator | sudo bash  Upgrading Airgap Installs Airgap installations can be upgraded by downloading a newer version of the Replicated release, uncompressing it and re-running the install script using the airgap flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Replicated with the Easy Install Script</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing-via-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing-via-script/</guid>
      <description>We provide an easy-to-use one-line installation process (via shell script) which will detect your OS, ask a few questions and install both docker-engine and the required Replicated components.
If you want to always release your application with a specific version of Replicated you can read how to always install a specific version of Replicated.
 Basic Install  Save the install script to file and run. We recommend reading and understanding the install script prior to running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manually Installing Replicated</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing-manually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing-manually/</guid>
      <description>If you choose not to run the installation script use this guide; note that the install script also installs Docker, detects network configuration and allows proxy settings and provides support to auto-upgrade Replicated during your application release cycle.
To manually install start by checking you are running on a support operating system and follow the 4 steps.
1. Install Docker We recommend Docker version 17.06.2-ce. Refer to the Docker Installation Guide for Debian, Ubuntu, CentOS, Fedora, or RHEL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airgapped Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/airgapped-installations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/airgapped-installations/</guid>
      <description>An &amp;ldquo;airgapped&amp;rdquo; environment is a network that has no path to inbound or outbound internet traffic at all. Some enterprise customers require that you ship a package they can install in their airgapped environment.
Replicated supports this type of installation, using the following steps:
 Prepare the environment  The customer will be responsible for delivering a server running a supported version of Docker. Replicated supports Docker from 1.7.1 to 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/automating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/automating/</guid>
      <description>Replicated has support for automated installation and configuration. This feature is built for bootstrapping new installations and not for managing existing installations.
These steps must be run before installing Replicated. Replicated will only check for these values during initial installation.
Configure Replicated Automatically During installation, Replicated will create a config file in /etc/replicated.conf. If this file exists, the installer will not overwrite it. To configure Replicated, create this file using any or all of the following options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Nodes To A Replicated Cluster</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/add-nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/add-nodes/</guid>
      <description>When an application is configured by the vendor with a clustering strategy, Replicated makes it possible for the end customer to install additional nodes on remote instances to run a distributed application. Installations of Replicated using the easy installation script will install an operator on the local node automatically.
On the Cluster page on the On-Prem Console an &amp;ldquo;Add Node&amp;rdquo; button will be visible. This will prompt the end customer with two simple options for adding a node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Replicated 1.2</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing-1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/installing-1.2/</guid>
      <description>Old Version Warning
The content in this document is for a previous version of Replicated. If you are looking for the current version, it is available at /distributing-an-application/installing/
 Host Setup Before installing your app, you need to install Replicated on a compatible machine.
Supported Operating Systems We support the server versions of the following OS&amp;rsquo;s
 Debian 7.7+ Ubuntu 14.04 / 15.10 Fedora 21 / 22 Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Replicated 1.2</title>
      <link>/docs/native/customer-installations/upgrading-1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 04:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/native/customer-installations/upgrading-1.2/</guid>
      <description>Old Version Warning
The content in this document is for a previous version of Replicated. If you are looking for the current version, it is available at /here.
 You may need to add the Replicated repository and GPG key to the package manager before running commands, see Manual Installation for more details.
Ubuntu/Debian apt-get update apt-get install replicated replicated-ui replicated-agent  CentOS/RHEL/Fedora yum makecache yum update replicated replicated-ui replicated-agent  If you have additional nodes you will independently need to run the following on each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>